Guide to the Lady St. Helier Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence
  - LEIGHTON OF STRETTON, FREDERIC LEIGHTON, BARON
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 235)
  - LEOPOLD, PRINCE, DUKE OF ALBANY
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1882 Jan 9 (Box 4, Folder 236)
  - LEWIS, RICHARD, BP. OF LLANDAFF
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1883 Feb 6 (Box 4, Folder 237)
  - LIGHTFOOT, JOSEPH BARBER, BP. OF DURHAM
    - 3 ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1886-88 (Box 4, Folder 238)
  - LILLY, WILLIAM SAMUEL
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1887, 1890 (Box 4, Folder 239)
  - LINCOLN, ROBERT TODD
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1891 Apr 17 (Box 4, Folder 240)
  - LISTER, JOSEPH, BARON
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1897 Jan 7 (Box 4, Folder 241)
  - LLANDAFF, HENRY MATTHEWS, VISCOUNT
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1886 Aug 4 (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - 11 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1889-1912 (Box 4, Folder 243)
  - LOCKE, WILLIAM JOHN
    - 5 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 244)
  - LOCKWOOD, FRANK, SIR
    - 4 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1890-95, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 245)
    - ALS to Lord Midleton, 1897 Apr 20 (Box 4, Folder 246)
  - LOHR, MARIE
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 247)
  - LONG, EDWIN LONGSDEN
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1888 Aug 6 (Box 4, Folder 248)
  - LOUISE, DUCHESS OF ARGYLL
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1903, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 249)
  - LOWELL, JAMES RUSSELL
    - ALS, AL in the third person, and AMS of rhymed message to Lady St. Helier (Box 4, Folder 250)
  - LOWNDES, MARIE ADELAIDE
    - TLS and ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1929, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 251)
  - LUDLOW, HENRY CHARLES LOPES, BARON
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1888 Feb 23 (Box 4, Folder 252)
  - LUGARD, FLORA LOUISE, LADY
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - 8 ALS to Lady Midleton, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - LYNCH, ARTHUR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1906 Jun 21 (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - LYTTELTON, ALFRED
    - ALS to Lady Midleton, 1905 Feb 13 (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - LYTTON, EDWARD ROBERT BULWER-LYTTON, EARL OF
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 257)
  - MACDONALD, HECTOR ARCHIBALD, SIR
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1899, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - 2 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1894, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - MAHAN, ALFRED THAYER
    - 10 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1894-1905, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - ALS to Lady Midleton, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - MALLOCK, WILLIAM HURRELL
    - 3 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1904-06 (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - MARY, DUCHESS OF GLOUCESTER
    - ALS to Lady Midleton, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - MARY ADELAIDE WILHELMINA ELIZABETH, DUCHESS OF TECK
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1890 Jan 27 (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - MASON, ALFRED EDWARD WOODLEY
    - 5 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1917, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - 17 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 267-268)
    - ALS to Lady Midleton, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - MASTERMAN, CHARLES FREDERICK GURNEY
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1907 Dec 6 (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - MATHERS, HELEN
    See: Helen Buckingham Reeves, Box 5, folder 308
  - MAUGHAM, W. SOMERSET (WILLIAM SOMERSET)
    - 5 ALS (one incomplete) to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - MCCLINTOCK, FRANCIS LEOPOLD, SIR
    - AL in the third person to Baron St. Helier, 1893 Jul 7 (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - MCKENNA, REGINALD
    - 2 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - MENDES-FRANCE, PIERRE
    - TLS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1955 Feb 21 (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - MEYNELL, VIOLA
    - 2 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - MIDDLETON, RICHARD WILLIAM EVELYN
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1898 Feb 19 (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - MIDLETON, WILLIAM ST. JOHN FREMANTLE BRODRICK, EARL OF
    - ALS to Lady Midleton, 1898 Aug 3 (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - MILLAIS, JOHN EVERETT, SIR
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1896 Mar 2 (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - MILNER, ALFRED MILNER, VISCOUNT
    - 2 ALS to Lady Midleton, 1909, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - MONYPENNY, WILLIAM FLAVELLE
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1907 May 30 (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - MORIER, ROBERT, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1889 Jul 16 (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - MORLEY, JOHN MORLEY, VISCOUNT
    - 3 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1887-97 (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - ALS to Lady Midleton, 1907 Nov 11 (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - MORRIS, LEWIS, SIR
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1892, 1897 (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - Christmas card to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - MORRIS, MICHAEL MORRIS, BARON
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - MOULTON, JOHN FLETCHER MOULTON, BARON
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1914 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - MOULTON, LOUISE CHANDLER
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - MURRAY, GEORGE HERBERT
    - ALS to Charles Russell, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - NEWTON, CHARLES THOMAS, SIR
    - ALS to "Dear Stanley", 1876 Jun 6 (Box 5, Folder 290)
  - NOVIKOVA, OLGA ALEKSIEEVNA
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 291)
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1892 Mar 15 (Box 5, Folder 292)
  - O'CONNOR, THOMAS POWER
    - TLS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1926 Aug 4 (Box 5, Folder 293)
  - ONSLOW, WILLIAM HILLIER ONSLOW, EARL OF
    - TLS to Lord Midleton, 1904 Mar 17 (Box 5, Folder 294)
  - PAGE, THOMAS NELSON
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1906 Sep 5 (Box 5, Folder 295)
  - PAGET, JAMES, SIR
    - 3 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1889-97 (Box 5, Folder 296)
  - PAGET, VIOLET
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1896 Feb 21 (Box 5, Folder 297)
  - PARKER, GILBERT, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1910 Jan 30 (Box 5, Folder 298)
  - PAUNCEFOTE, JULIAN, BARON
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1899 Aug 8 (Box 5, Folder 299)
  - PHELPS, EDWARD JOHN
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1886, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 300)
    - 2 ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1888, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 301)
  - PHILLIPS, STEPHEN
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 302)
  - POYNTER, EDWARD JOHN, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1913 Jun 10 (Box 5, Folder 303)
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1896 Nov 10 (Box 5, Folder 304)
    - ALS to "Miss Stanley", 1883 Nov 11 (Box 5, Folder 305)
  - PRIESTLEY, WILLIAM OVEREND, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1888 Jul 21 (Box 5, Folder 306)
  - QUAIN, RICHARD, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 307)
  - REEVES, HELEN BUCKINGHAM
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1904 Apr 14 (Box 5, Folder 308)
  - REHAN, ADA
    - 3 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1892-96 (Box 5, Folder 309)
  - RHODES, CECIL
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 310)
  - RICHMOND, WILLIAM BLAKE, SIR
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1897 Jun 23 (Box 5, Folder 311)
  - RIDGE, WILLIAM PETT
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 312)
  - RIDLEY, MATTHEW WHITE, VISCOUNT
    - 2 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1902, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 313)
  - RIGBY, JOHN, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1892 Nov 7 (Box 5, Folder 314)
  - RITCHIE, ANNE ISABELLE (THACKERAY), LADY
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 315)
  - RIVES, AMÉLIE
    See: Amélie Rives-Chandler Troubetzkoy, Box 6, folder 385
  - ROBERTS, FREDERICK SLEIGH ROBERTS, EARL
    - 7 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1898-1912 (Box 5, Folder 316)
    - ALS and TLS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1912, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 317)
  - ROBINS, ELIZABETH
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 318)
  - ROOSEVELT, THEODORE
    - 4 TLS to Lady St. Helier, 1910-18 (Box 5, Folder 319)
  - ROSEBERY, ARCHIBALD PHILIP PRIMROSE, EARL OF
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1890, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 320)
  - ROWTON, MONTAGU WILLIAM LOWRY-CORRY, BARON
    - 3 ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 321)
    - 10 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1898-1900, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 322)
    - ALS to Lady Midleton, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 323)
  - RUMBOLD, HORACE, SIR
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1897 Jun 24 (Box 5, Folder 324)
  - RUSSELL, CHARLES, BARON
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1892, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 325)
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1897 Jun 20 (Box 5, Folder 326)
  - RUSSELL, MARY ANNETTE BEAUCHAMP RUSSELL, COUNTESS
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 327)
  - RUSSELL, WILLIAM HOWARD, SIR
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1878, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 328)
  - SACKVILLE-WEST, VITA (VICTORIA)
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 329)
  - ST. ALDWYN OF COLN, MICHAEL EDWARD, VISCOUNT
    See: Sir Michael Edward Hicks Beach, Box 4, folder 207
  - SAINTON-DOLBY, CHARLOTTE HELEN
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 330)
  - SALA, GEORGE AUGUSTUS
    - ALS to "My dear Edmund" (Box 5, Folder 331)
    - Dinner menu inscribed to "Mrs. Jeune" (Lady St. Helier), 1890 Jun 23 (Box 5, Folder 332)
  - SALISBURY, JAMES EDWARD GASCOYNE-CECIL, MARQUESS OF
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1917 Mar 14 (Box 5, Folder 333)
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1889 Nov 24 (Box 5, Folder 334)
  - SALISBURY, ROBERT ARTHUR GASCOYNE-CECIL, MARQUESS OF
    - 4 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1894-1904, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 335)
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1897 Jun 15 (Box 5, Folder 336)
    - ALS to Lord Midleton, 1900 Nov 6 (Box 5, Folder 337)
  - SAMBOURNE, LINLEY
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1890, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 338)
  - SARGENT, JOHN SINGER
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 339)
  - SEAMAN, OWEN, SIR
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1907, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 340)
    - 6 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1906-08, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 341)
  - SEDGWICK, ANNE DOUGLAS
    - 7 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1909-17, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 342)
  - SELBOURNE, ROUNDELL PALMER, EARL OF
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1891 May 19 (Box 5, Folder 343)
      Accompanied by typescript, signed, concerning a subscription for a memorial to the Archbishop of York [William Connor Magee].
    - 2 ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1889, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 344)
  - SELBY, WILLIAM COURT GULLY, VISCOUNT
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1895 Apr 21 (Box 5, Folder 345)
  - SLATIN, RUDOLF CARL, FREIHERR VON
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 346)
  - SMALLEY, GEORGE WASHBURN
    - ALS to Lady Stanley, 1900 Feb 24 (Box 5, Folder 347)
  - SMITH, GOLDWIN
    - 3 ALS, 2 LS, and 2 TL to Lady St. Helier, 1899-1909, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 348)
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1881 Jun 20 (Box 5, Folder 349)
  - SMITH, WILLIAM, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1875 Dec 31 (Box 5, Folder 350)
  - SMITH, WILLIAM HENRY
    - 2 ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1887, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 351)
    - ALS to Lord Midleton, 1886 Dec 31 (Box 5, Folder 352)
  - SMUTS, JAN CHRISTIAAN
    - 2 TLS to Lady St. Helier, 1917, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 353)
  - SPEED, T.
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1886 Jun 5 (Box 5, Folder 354)
  - STAAL, EGOR EGOROVICH, BARON
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 355)
  - STANHOPE, EDWARD
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 356)
  - STANHOPE, PHILIP HENRY, EARL
    - ALS to "Colonel Stanley", 1873 Dec 20 (Box 5, Folder 357)
  - STANLEY, ARTHUR PENRHYN
    - ALS to "Mrs. Stanley", 1880 (Box 5, Folder 358)
  - STARK, FREYA
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1950 Nov 24 (Box 5, Folder 359)
  - STEEL, FLORA ANNIE WEBSTER
    - 5 ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 360)
  - STEWART, DONALD MARTIN, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 361)
  - STEPHEN, JAMES FITZJAMES, SIR
    - 6 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1879-80, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 362)
    - 2 ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1882, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 363)
  - STREET, GEORGE SLYTHE
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 364)
    - 2 ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 365)
  - STUBBS, WILLIAM, BP. OF OXFORD
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1890 Nov 24 (Box 5, Folder 366)
  - TENNIEL, JOHN, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1888 Feb 13 (Box 6, Folder 367)
  - TERRY, ELLEN, DAME
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1904 Mar 20 (Box 6, Folder 368)
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 369)
  - TERRY, MARION
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 370)
  - THOMPSON, HENRY, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1890 Aug 30 (Box 6, Folder 371)
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1882 Aug 14 (Box 6, Folder 372)
    - 99 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1892-1902, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 373-379)
    - 7 ALS to Lady Midleton, 1893-1902, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 380)
    - 2 ALS to "Madeleine and Dorothy", 1892, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 381)
  - THURSTON, ERNEST TEMPLE
    - 20 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 382)
  - TOWNSHEND, CHARLES VERE FERRERS, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1896 Apr 25 (Box 6, Folder 383)
      Accompanied by an AMS program of musical entertainment headed "Camp Fire, Akasheh 24-4-96" and an envelope.
  - TREVELYAN, GEORGE OTTO, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1889 Apr 2 (Box 6, Folder 384)
  - TROUBETZKOY, AMÉLIE RIVES-CHANDLER
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 385)
  - UNIDENTIFIED
    - 2 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1899, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 386)
  - VACHELL, HORACE ANNESLEY
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 387)
    - 15 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1908-15, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 388)
  - VAMBÉRY, ARMIN
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 389)
  - VICTORIA, QUEEN OF GREAT BRITAIN
    - DS appointing Henry Eden Allhusen to Her Majesty's Yeomanry Forces, 1891 May 6 (Box 6, Folder 390)
  - VILLIERS, CHARLES PELHAM
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1875, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 391)
  - WALERAN, WILLIAM HOOD WALROND, BARON
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1902 Jul 1 (Box 6, Folder 392)
  - WALPOLE, HUGH, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1922 Jul 11 (Box 6, Folder 393)
  - WARBURTON, ROBERT, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 394)
  - WARD, EDWARD WILLIS DUNCAN, SIR
    - 3 ALS to Lady Midleton, 1903-04 (Box 6, Folder 395)
  - WARD, MARY AUGUSTA (MRS. HUMPHRY WARD)
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1896 Jul 12 (Box 6, Folder 396)
  - WATSON, HENRY BRERETON MARRIOTT
    - AL fragment to unidentified, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 397)
  - WATSON, WILLIAM, SIR
    - ALS to "Miss Stanley", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 398)
  - WATTS-DUNTON, THEODORE
    - ALS to "Mr. Jones", 1888 May 23 (Box 6, Folder 399)
  - WELLDON, JAMES EDWARD COWELL, BP.
    - TLS to Lady St. Helier, 1926 Aug 28 (Box 6, Folder 400)
    - 36 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1897-1910 (Box 6, Folder 401-403)
    - 11 ALS to Lady Midleton, 1898-1903 (Box 6, Folder 404)
    - TLS to "Lady Tweeddale", 1926 Sep 1 (Box 6, Folder 405)
  - WELLS, H. G. (HERBERT GEORGE)
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1899 Jun 23 (Box 6, Folder 406)
  - WHARTON, EDITH
    - 36 ALS and 2 TLS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1920-37, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 407-408)
  - WHITE, GEORGE STUART, SIR
    - ALS to Lord Midleton, 1900 Jun 16 (Box 6, Folder 409)
  - WILBERFORCE, ALBERT BASIL ORME
    - ALS to "Dear Mr. Hogg", 1892 Apr 6 (Box 6, Folder 410)
  - WILLCOCKS, JAMES, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1913 Jul 19 (Box 6, Folder 411)
  - WILLS, ALFRED, SIR
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1888 15 Feb (Box 6, Folder 412)
  - WILSON, GUY DOUGLAS ARTHUR FLEETWOOD, SIR
    - ALS to Lord Midleton, [1895?] (Box 6, Folder 413)
  - WINGATE, FRANCIS REGINALD, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1906 Jun 25 (Box 6, Folder 414)
  - WINNINGTON-INGRAM, ARTHUR FOLEY, BP.
    - ALS to Lady Midleton, 1905 Jan 3 (Box 6, Folder 415)
  - WOLFF, HENRY DRUMMOND, SIR
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1891 Apr 9 (Box 6, Folder 416)
    - ALS to Baron St. Helier, 1892 Jan 24 (Box 6, Folder 417)
  - WOLSELEY, GARNET JOSEPH WOLSELEY, VISCOUNT
    - ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1900 Jan 2 (Box 7, Folder 418)
    - 4 ALS to Lord Midleton, 1889-96, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 419)
  - WOOD, EVELYN, SIR
    - 2 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1894, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 420)
    - 68 ALS and TLS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1894-1909, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 421-426)
    - TLS to "My dear Allhusen", 1901 Aug 16 (Box 7, Folder 427)
    - 11 ALS to Lady Midleton, 1898-1903 (Box 7, Folder 428)
  - WOODHAM-SMITH, CECIL BLANCHE FITZGERALD
    - TLS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1955 Jan 4 (Box 7, Folder 429)
  - WRIGHT, ALMROTH EDWARD, SIR
    - 2 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 430)
  - YEATS-BROWN, FRANCIS CHARLES CLAYPON
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 431)
  - YOUNG, FILSON
    - ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1911 May 14 (Box 7, Folder 432)
  - YPRES, JOHN DENTON PINKSTONE FRENCH, EARL OF
    - 3 ALS to Lady St. Helier, 1916-21 (Box 7, Folder 433)
    - 2 ALS to Dorothy Stanley Allhusen, 1907, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 434)
    - ALS to Lady Midleton, 1907 Nov 15 (Box 7, Folder 435)